<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robby&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://robby.santoslab.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Robby&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://robby.santoslab.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://robby.santoslab.org/funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robby.santoslab.org/funding/</guid>
      <description>Funding MAILLE: Microkernal Application Information fLow with Logic-based Enforcement
Co-PI, with John Hatcliff (K-State PI); and Todd Carpenter (Lead PI) at Adventium Labs.
U.S. Air Force Research Laboratory (AFRL) Small Business Innovation Research (SBIR) Phase II. Project total: $749,957 (K-State&amp;rsquo;s portion: $347,000). Duration: May 2021 - April 2023.
SIRFUR: Software Implementation from Rigorous Formal Usable Requirements
K-State PI, with John Hatcliff (co-PI); and Todd Carpenter (Lead PI) at Adventium Labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://robby.santoslab.org/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robby.santoslab.org/papers/</guid>
      <description>Recent Papers Jason Belt, John Hatcliff, Robby, John Shackleton, Jim Carciofini, Todd Carpenter, Eric Mercer, Isaac Amundson, Junaid Babar, Darren Cofer, David Hardin, Karl Hoech, Konrad Slind, Ihor Kuz, Kent McLeod: Model-driven development for the seL4 microkernel using the HAMR framework. JSA 134: 102789, 2023.
John Hatcliff, Danielle Stewart, Jason Belt, Robby: An AADL Contract Language Supporting Integrated Model- and Code-Level Verification. HILT 2022 (to appear).
Hariharan Thiagarajan, John Hatcliff, Robby: Awas: AADL information flow and error propagation analysis framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://robby.santoslab.org/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robby.santoslab.org/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Current Sireum &amp;ndash; A High Assurance System Engineering Platform Past Bandera &amp;ndash; a software model checker for concurrent Java programs
Bogor &amp;ndash; a software model checking framework
Cadena &amp;ndash; an Eclipse-based extensible integrated modeling and development framework for component-based systems
JMLEclipse &amp;ndash; an Eclipse-based front-end for the Java Modeling Language (JML)
MDCF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://robby.santoslab.org/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robby.santoslab.org/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching CIS 706/801: Translator Design I &amp;amp; II
The course teaches modern compiler techniques applied to general-purpose programming language. The goal of the course is to give students a working knowledge of the foundations, tools, and engineering approaches used in developing formal language translators. The emphasis is on the construction of compilers to position students to build translators for little languages in their careers.
CIS 301: Logical Foundations of Programming</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
